## **MIKAELLA PICONES**

# WEB DEVELOPER & APP SUPPORT ANALYST

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a dedicated web developer who also worked on application support with 2 plus years of experience with the ability to take responsibility for implementing and completing complex assignments. Willing to learn, highly organized with attention to detail and a great track record of managing multiple priorities.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Accenture Inc.

Java Bootcamp | Aug 2018 - Oct 2018 Project ASM-R | Oct 2018 - Current

- Fixed bugs and developed multiple enhancements for our client's web application eliminating the need for change requests for reduced request turn-around time using Java, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS, jQueryUI, JSP, Javascript
- Supported multiple applications within the project via troubleshooting, analyzing, investigating and resolving issues raised by our client through coordinating with multiple teams & including the client as needed.
- Created functional and technical documentations

#### Web Development Intern

Fortcode Inc. | Jun 2017 - Aug 2017

 Developed an employee time management web application using NodeJS, Express, VueJS, HTML (Pug), PostgreSQL and created unit tests with Mocha and Istanbul through Agile (Scrum)

#### Freelance

Champion Marketing | Aug 2016 - Dec 2016

 Developed an online ordering system to automate the client's business process using PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

#### EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

#### Lady Mediatrix Institute

Elementary to High School | 2005 - 2014

• Graduated in Year 2014

#### **University of Santo Tomas**

BS Computer Science | 2014 - 2018

- Major in Game Development
- Two-time Dean's Lister

### CONTACT ME AT

- Home Address: 406 Highway View, Masin Sur, Candelaria, Ouezon
- mikaellaspicones@gmail.com
- mikpicones.github.io/portfolio
- in /mikaella-picones-4972b9144

#### SKILLS SUMMARY

Front-end Development (HTML, CSS, SASS, Pug, jQueryUI, JSP,ReactJS, VueJS)

Back-end Development (Java, NodeJS, PHP, Python)

Design Frameworks (Material-UI, Bootstrap)

RDBMS (MySQL, PostgreSQL)

Versioning Control (Git, SVN)

Agile Methodology (Scrum)

Adobe Photoshop

IDE (Eclipse, Visual Studio)